Guide to the Mabou Mines Archive, 1966-2000 (bulk 1970-1995) MSS.133
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series III: Production Files, 146646
  - Subseries A: Mabou Mines stage productions, 146691
    - The Bribe Saratoga Internation Theater Institute: negative reply, 1994; 146719 (Box 19, Folder 828)
    - The Bribe box office records: Theater for the New City, Ontological, etc., 1993; 146718 (Box 19, Folder 829)
    - The Bribe development, 1986-1994; 146717 (Box 19, Folder 830)
    - The Bribe budget, 1986-1988; 146716 (Box 19, Folder 831)
    - The Bribe budget, 1993; 146715 (Box 19, Folder 832)
    - The Bribe / The MahabharANTa expenses, receipts, 1992; 146714 (Box 19, Folder 833)
    - The Bribe expenses, receipts April, 1993; 146713 (Box 19, Folder 834)
    - The MahabharANTa "The Insect Who Loved the World" correspondence, bios, press, etc., 1991; 146712 (Box 19, Folder 835)
    - The MahabharANTa notes and correspondence between company members, 1992; 146711 (Box 19, Folder 836)
    - The MahabharANTa correspondence between Larry Reed and Lee Breuer, 1992; 146710 (Box 19, Folder 837)
    - The MahabharANTa program information, undated; 146709 (Box 19, Folder 838)
    - The MahabharANTa technical, undated; 146708 (Box 19, Folder 839)
    - The MahabharANTa description, press release, undated; 146707 (Box 19, Folder 840)
    - The MahabharANTa I Wayan Wija, Balinese puppeteer: CV, photograph, press, 1992; 146706 (Box 19, Folder 841)
    - The MahabharANTa agreements, 1985-1992; 146705 (Box 19, Folder 842)
    - The MahabharANTa St. Ann's, 1992; 146704 (Box 19, Folder 843)
    - The MahabharANTa International Festival of Puppet Theater, 1992; 146703 (Box 19, Folder 844)
    - The MahabharANTa SUNY Stonybrook, 1992; 146702 (Box 19, Folder 845)
    - The MahabharANTa Bali, 1992; 146701 (Box 19, Folder 846)
    - The MahabharANTa Arizona State University, Phoenix, 1992; 146700 (Box 19, Folder 847)
    - The MahabharANTa Tisch School of the Arts, NYU, 1992; 146699 (Box 19, Folder 848)
    - The MahabharANTa Lower Manhattan Cultural Council, 1992; 146698 (Box 19, Folder 849)
    - The MahabharANTa Atlanta Center for Puppetry Arts, 1992; 146697 (Box 19, Folder 850)
    - The MahabharANTa MIT, 1992; 146696 (Box 19, Folder 851)
    - The MahabharANTa correspondence, inquiries, 1992-1993; 146695 (Box 19, Folder 852)
    - The MahabharANTa development, 1992; 146694 (Box 19, Folder 853)
    - The MahabharANTa budget: NY tour, undated; 146693 (Box 19, Folder 854)
    - The MahabharANTa box office records Oct 13-Nov 16, 1992; 146692 (Box 19, Folder 855)
    - Dead End Kids light cue sheets, tracking sheets and notes (Mark Taper Forum, Dock Street Theater), ca. 1980-1984; 147694 (Box 109, Folder 2277)
      Scripts, checking account files & stubs, press, screening info, etc.
      Offsite Barcode: 31142042236151
    - Dead End Kids hook-up sheets, star template, groundplans, ca. 1980-1984; 147698 (Box 109, Folder 2278)
      Finances, press, resumes, screening info, mailing lists, etc.
    - Dead End Kids press, ca. 1980-1984; 147699 (Box 109, Folder 2279)
      Press, distribution info, grants, finances, etc.
    - Dead End Kids touring files, ca. 1980-1984; 147700 (Box 109, Folder 2280)
      Funding, distributioon info, film festival files, etc.
    - Dead End Kids script and notes, ca. 1981-1983; 147701 (Box 109, Folder 2281)
      Technical files, touring info, etc.
    - Reel to Real income and disbursments ledger; accounts payable journal, 1993-1994; 147706 (Box 111, Folder 2300)
      Finances, screenings, promotional material, workshop info, lighting and equipment files, grants, etc.
      Offsite Barcode: 31142042236177
    - Reel to Real early notes, 1990-1991; 152011 (Box 111, Folder 2301)
    - Reel to Real production files, 1991-1992; 152012 (Box 111, Folder 2302)
    - Reel to Real script development, undated; 152014 (Box 111, Folder 2303)
    - Reel to Real equipment lists, 1993-1994; 152016 (Box 111, Folder 2304)
    - Reel to Real sketches for set, 1994; 152017 (Box 111, Folder 2305)
    - Reel to Real The Theatre Institute at Storm King files, 1990-1991; 152018 (Box 111, Folder 2306)
    - Reel to Real flyer mock-up, 1994; 152019 (Box 111, Folder 2307)
    - Reel to Real video files, 1992-1993; 152020 (Box 111, Folder 2308)
    - Reel to Real class notes, 1992; 152021 (Box 111, Folder 2309)
    - Reel to Real workshop, Arizona State University West, 1994; 152022 (Box 111, Folder 2310)
    - Reel to Real workshop, Bucknell University, 1994; 152023 (Box 111, Folder 2311)
    - Reel to Real The Kitchen premiere, 1994; 152024 (Box 111, Folder 2312)
    - Reel to Real Duke University production files, 1994; 152025 (Box 111, Folder 2313)
    - Reel to Real inquiries, 1990-1994; 152026 (Box 111, Folder 2314)
    - Reel to Real biographical material, N/A; 152027 (Box 111, Folder 2315)
    - Reel to Real Al Kryszak files [incl. photo and slides], 1993; 152028 (Box 111, Folder 2316)
    - Reel to Real New York University files, 1993; 152029 (Box 111, Folder 2317)
    - Reel to Real Yellow Springs Institute files, 1992-1994; 152030 (Box 111, Folder 2318)
    - Reel to Real touring files, 1994; 152031 (Box 111, Folder 2319)
    - Reel to Real correspondence, 1990-1994; 152032 (Box 111, Folder 2320)
    - Reel to Real NYSCA film application files, 1994; 152033 (Box 111, Folder 2321)
    - Reel to Real development files, 1994; 152034 (Box 111, Folder 2322)
    - Reel to Real film financial files, 1993-1994; 152035 (Box 111, Folder 2323)
    - Reel to Real ASU West fincancial files, 1993; 152036 (Box 111, Folder 2324)
    - Reel to Real Bucknell University financial files, 1993-1994; 152037 (Box 111, Folder 2325)
    - Reel to Real The Kitchen financial files, 1994; 152038 (Box 111, Folder 2326)
    - Reel to Real financial files, 1993-1994; 152039 (Box 111, Folder 2327)
    - Reel to Real financial files, 1993-1994; 152040 (Box 111, Folder 2328)
    - Animal Magnetism scripts [drafts] w/ related project notes and misc. files, 1994; 152041 (Box 111, Folder 2329)
    - Benefits - committee mailing lists, 1982-1985; 147707 (Box 112, Folder 2330)
      Incl. files for benefits, Grey Art Gallery, Animal Magnetism, and Lear.
      Offsite Barcode: 31142042236185
    - 15th Anniversary Benefit - individual donors, 1985; 152042 (Box 112, Folder 2331)
    - 15th Anniversary Benefit - thank yous, 1985; 152043 (Box 112, Folder 2332)
    - 15th Anniversary Benefit files, 1985; 152044 (Box 112, Folder 2333)
    - Benefit files, 1986; 152045 (Box 112, Folder 2334)
    - Benefit budgets, 1986; 152046 (Box 112, Folder 2335)
    - Beckett Benefit files, 1986; 152047 (Box 112, Folder 2336)
    - Friends Seminary Benefit, 1988; 152048 (Box 112, Folder 2337)
    - 20th Anniversary promotional material, 1990; 152049 (Box 112, Folder 2338)
    - 20th Anniversary info, 1990; 152050 (Box 112, Folder 2339)
    - 20th Anniversary - Grey Art Gallery checklist, plans and report, 1990; 152051 (Box 112, Folder 2340)
    - 20th Anniversary - Grey Art Gallery press, 1990; 152052 (Box 112, Folder 2341)
    - Indonesia Benefit, 1992-1993; 152053 (Box 112, Folder 2342)
    - Misc. unidentified set effects slides, undated; 152137 (Box 112, Folder 2373)
  - Subseries B: Mabou Mines artist-in-residence programs, 146662
    Files from productions of Re-Cher-Chez, a studio for avant-garde performing arts, and Mabou Mines/Suite, the company's artists-in-residence/theater training program.
    - Re-Cher-Chez grant applications, descriptions, bios, press, budgets, 1979-1981; 146690 (Box 20, Folder 856)
      Offsite Barcode: 31142042235930
    - Re-Cher-Chez announcements, programs, photos, contact sheets, 1980-1991; 146689 (Box 20, Folder 857)
    - Re-Cher-Chez statement by Lisa Lorwin Aug 28, 1981; 146688 (Box 20, Folder 858)
    - Re-Cher-Chez photos: Mayfest, 1984; 146687 (Box 20, Folder 859)
    - Mabou Mines/Suite press release, 1991-1992; 146686 (Box 20, Folder 860)
    - Mabou Mines/Suite proposal by Joanna Adler, 1992; 146685 (Box 20, Folder 861)
    - Mabou Mines/Suite flyers, contact sheets, mailing lists, press releases, 1991-1992; 146684 (Box 20, Folder 862)
    - Mabou Mines/Suite artists' performances, 1992-1993; 146683 (Box 20, Folder 863)
    - Mabou Mines/Suite Suite Dreams: the studio conversion campaign for Mabou Mines/Suite, 1992; 146682 (Box 20, Folder 864)
    - Mabou Mines/Suite funding, 1992-1993; 146681 (Box 20, Folder 865)
    - Mabou Mines/Suite performances of resident artists after residency, 1992-1993; 146680 (Box 20, Folder 866)
    - Mabou Mines/Suite flyer, 1993-1994; 146679 (Box 20, Folder 867)
    - Mabou Mines/Suite artists' performances: programs, promotional material, 1993-1994; 146678 (Box 20, Folder 868)
    - Mabou Mines/Suite resident artist applications/proposals, 1993-1994; 146677 (Box 20, Folder 869)
    - Mabou Mines/Suite resident artist applications/proposals, 1993-1994; 146676 (Box 20, Folder 870)
    - Mabou Mines/Suite resident artist agreements, 1993-1994; 146675 (Box 20, Folder 871)
    - Mabou Mines/Suite resident artist program, 1993-1994; 146674 (Box 20, Folder 872)
    - Mabou Mines/Suite resident artist program, 1993-1994; 146673 (Box 20, Folder 873)
    - Mabou Mines/Suite "Circus Circus" script by D.C. Latham, 1994; 146672 (Box 20, Folder 874)
    - Mabou Mines/Suite resident artist funding initiatives, 1994; 146671 (Box 20, Folder 875)
    - Mabou Mines/Suite 1994 calendar with notes, 146670 (Box 20, Folder 876)
    - Mabou Mines/Suite resident artist program, 1994-1995; 146669 (Box 20, Folder 877)
    - Mabou Mines/Suite resident artist program: not accepted, 1994-1995; 146668 (Box 20, Folder 878)
    - Mabou Mines/Suite development: grant applications, 1994; 146667 (Box 20, Folder 879)
    - Mabou Mines/Suite resident artist script: "Ha" by Dawn Akemi Saito, 1995; 146666 (Box 20, Folder 880)
    - Mabou Mines/Suite resident artist flyers, 1995; 146665 (Box 20, Folder 881)
    - Mabou Mines/Suite resident artist performances, 1995; 146664 (Box 20, Folder 882)
    - Mabou Mines/Suite performances of resident artists after residency, 1995; 146663 (Box 20, Folder 883)
  - Subseries C: Mabou Mines-related productions, 146647
    Files from productions involving members and affiliates of Mabou Mines.
    - Isabelle Eberhardt Yellow Springs Insititute correspondence, 1988-1989; 146661 (Box 20, Folder 884)
    - Isabelle Eberhardt budgets, tech notes Nov-Dec, 1988; 146660 (Box 20, Folder 885)
    - Lies video, 1981; 146659 (Box 20, Folder 886)
    - Lies "The Lie" manuscript/typescript, undated; 146658 (Box 20, Folder 887)
    - Lies "The Lie" manuscript/typescript, undated; 146657 (Box 20, Folder 888)
    - Lies "The Lie" manuscript/typescript; "add-ons, new scenes, changes, notes, etc.", undated; 146656 (Box 20, Folder 889)
    - Lies "The Lie" manuscript/typescript; "add-ons, new scenes, changes, notes, etc.", undated; 146655 (Box 20, Folder 890)
    - Lulu statement, correspondence, grant application, 1991; 146654 (Box 20, Folder 891)
    - Lulu correspondence, funding, 1990-1992; 146653 (Box 20, Folder 892)
    - The Martian Project featuring Joanna Adler; project description, bios, undated; 146652 (Box 20, Folder 893)
    - Voyage of the Beagle grant application, budget, fundraising, etc., 1985-1987; 146651 (Box 20, Folder 894)
    - Voyage of the Beagle miscellaneous brochures, undated; 146650 (Box 20, Folder 895)
    - Miscellaneous material poem: "Lee Laughs/Lee Lives/She Double Takes" by Lee Breuer, 1972; 146649 (Box 20, Folder 896)
    - Miscellaneous material birthday card to Lee Breuer; Seattle, WA, undated; 146648 (Box 20, Folder 897)
  - Subseries D: Mabou Mines film productions - Dead End Kids, 151109
    - Check stubs - film account (Chemical Bank), 2/83-3/87, 1983-1987; 151111 (Box 102, Folder 2049)
      Offsite Barcode: 31142042236086
    - Partial scripts (revised) - by castmember, undated; 151112 (Box 102, Folder 2050)
    - Press packets, 1986; 151113 (Box 102, Folder 2051)
    - Film script, undated; 151114 (Box 102, Folder 2052)
    - Letters of support/recommendation, 1983; 151115 (Box 102, Folder 2053)
      letters from: Joseph Papp, Lynne Littman, Helen Caldicott, Philip Glass, Susan Landau
    - 8"x8" Diskette, undated; 151116 (Box 102, Folder 2054)
    - Film screenings - correspondence, notes, and promotional material, 1986-1987; 151117 (Box 102, Folder 2055)
    - Publications - DEC Films catalogs (1985), Independent Feature FIlm Market program (10/85), Newsmagazine by Alberta Women (3-4/1987), 1985, 1987; 151118 (Box 102, Folder 2056)
    - Print/video disposition files, 1986; 151119 (Box 102, Folder 2057)
    - Proposal and brochures (incl. stage production material), 1981-1982; 151120 (Box 102, Folder 2058)
    - Women Make Movies V Festival, 1987; 151121 (Box 102, Folder 2059)
    - Misc. Film Festivals, 1987; 151122 (Box 102, Folder 2060)
    - Opticals worksheet (estimates), 1985; 151123 (Box 102, Folder 2061)
    - Film screening - 9/25/86, 1986; 151124 (Box 102, Folder 2062)
    - Film screening - 10/3/1986, 151125 (Box 102, Folder 2063)
    - Film screening - 10/8/86, 1986; 151126 (Box 102, Folder 2064)
    - Film screening & party - 11/5/86, 11/8/86, 1986; 151127 (Box 102, Folder 2065)
    - Dead End Kids screenplay (w/ staff and crew list, 10/14/82), 1982; 151128 (Box 102, Folder 2066)
    - Bill Kirksey files, 1985; 151141 (Box 102, Folder 2067)
    - Catalogs - The 9th, 10th, & 11th Hong Kong International Film Festival ('85-'87), AFI Festival Los Angeles ('87), 1985-1987; 151142 (Box 102, Folder 2068)
    - Misc. financial files, 1984-1985; 151143 (Box 102, Folder 2069)
    - Promotional expenses, 1985; 151144 (Box 102, Folder 2070)
    - Monty Diamond files, undated; 151145 (Box 102, Folder 2071)
    - Misc. administrative and financial files, 1981-1982; 151146 (Box 102, Folder 2072)
      incl. production budgets, correspondence, grants, etc.
    - Film screenings - 2/14/83 & 3/21/83, 1983; 151151 (Box 103, Folder 2073)
      Offsite Barcode: 31142042236094
    - Completion budget, 1985; 151152 (Box 103, Folder 2074)
    - Mailing lists, N/A; 151153 (Box 103, Folder 2075)
    - Michael Washburn & Associates files [funding/ contributions for stage production], 1980-1981; 151154 (Box 103, Folder 2076)
    - Film production budgets, 1982; 151155 (Box 103, Folder 2077)
    - Film production budgets (w/ deferments), 1982; 151156 (Box 103, Folder 2078)
    - Personnel biographies, N/A; 151157 (Box 103, Folder 2079)
    - Fact sheets & synopsis, N/A; 151158 (Box 103, Folder 2080)
    - Deferments, 1986; 151159 (Box 103, Folder 2081)
    - Du Art files, 1982-1985; 151160 (Box 103, Folder 2082)
    - Producers Services Group files, 1982-1984; 151161 (Box 103, Folder 2083)
    - Resumes, N/A; 151162 (Box 103, Folder 2084)
    - Staff letters-of-agreement, 1982-1985; 151163 (Box 103, Folder 2085)
    - Art - misc., 1985; 151164 (Box 103, Folder 2086)
    - Script breakdowns, 1985; 151165 (Box 103, Folder 2087)
    - Budget, 2/4/85, 1985; 151166 (Box 103, Folder 2088)
    - Call sheets, 2/85-3/85, 1985; 151167 (Box 103, Folder 2089)
    - Cash Receipts, 2/85-3/85, 1985; 151168 (Box 103, Folder 2090)
    - Correspondence, 2/85-3/85, 1985; 151169 (Box 103, Folder 2091)
    - Grip/electric packages, 2/85-3/85, 1985; 151170 (Box 103, Folder 2092)
    - Location forms, 1985; 151171 (Box 103, Folder 2093)
    - Music-related files/correspondence, 1983-1985; 151172 (Box 103, Folder 2094)
    - Office files/expenses, 1985; 151173 (Box 103, Folder 2095)
    - Misc. files, 2/85-3/85, 1985; 151174 (Box 103, Folder 2096)
    - Production reports, 2/85-3/85, 1985; 151175 (Box 103, Folder 2097)
    - Shooting schedules, script reports & sides, 2/85-3/85, 1985; 151176 (Box 103, Folder 2098)
    - Sound reports, 2/85-3/85, 1985; 151177 (Box 103, Folder 2099)
    - Vehicle rentals, 2/85, 1985; 151178 (Box 103, Folder 2100)
    - Wardrobe, 1985; 151179 (Box 103, Folder 2101)
    - Misc. research and production files, N/A; 151180 (Box 103, Folder 2102)
    - Editing, 1985-1986; 151181 (Box 103, Folder 2103)
    - Exhibitors (Film in the City), 1986; 151182 (Box 103, Folder 2104)
    - Releases, 2/85, 1985; 151183 (Box 103, Folder 2105)
    - Film-to-tape transfer articles, 1985; 151184 (Box 103, Folder 2106)
    - Deal memos & deferral agreements, 1985; 151185 (Box 103, Folder 2107)
    - Title and credits cards, N/A; 151186 (Box 104, Folder 2108)
      Offsite Barcode: 31142042236102
    - Women's Interart Center files, 1983; 151187 (Box 104, Folder 2109)
    - Foundation research, 1980-1986; 151188 (Box 104, Folder 2110)
    - Obie Award, for stage production [photocopy], 1981; 151189 (Box 104, Folder 2111)
    - Budgets & contributors, 1983-1986; 151190 (Box 104, Folder 2112)
    - NYSCA, 1985; 151191 (Box 104, Folder 2113)
    - Media Alliance, 1986; 151192 (Box 104, Folder 2114)
    - Chemical Bank files - film fund, 1982-1985; 151193 (Box 104, Folder 2115)
    - Distribution and press, 1986; 151194 (Box 104, Folder 2116)
    - Paid bills, 6/30/88, 1988; 151195 (Box 104, Folder 2117)
    - Distribution - correspondence, inquiries, & film mkt. list, 1986-1987; 151196 (Box 104, Folder 2118)
    - Independent feature market, 1983; 151197 (Box 104, Folder 2119)
    - Screen Actors Guild contract, 1987; 151198 (Box 104, Folder 2120)
    - ABC Video Enterprises files - correspondence, contracts, settlement, etc., 1982-1991; 151199 (Box 104, Folder 2122)
    - Island Pictures correspondence, 1985; 151200 (Box 104, Folder 2123)
    - Misc. prose, N/A; 151204 (Box 104, Folder 2124)
    - NEA files, 1984-1986; 151205 (Box 104, Folder 2125)
    - Sales tax exemption certificate, 1976; 151206 (Box 104, Folder 2126)
    - Sales and distribution, 1982-1986; 151207 (Box 104, Folder 2127)
    - Memos to company, 1985; 151208 (Box 104, Folder 2128)
    - Independent feature market, 1986; 151209 (Box 104, Folder 2129)
    - Blue Dolphin Film Distributors files, 1986-1987; 151210 (Box 104, Folder 2130)
    - SWAMP (Southwest Alternate Media Project) files, 1985; 151211 (Box 104, Folder 2131)
    - Rights inquiries & archival material, N/A; 151212 (Box 104, Folder 2132)
    - Academy Awards application form, 1985-1986; 151213 (Box 104, Folder 2133)
    - AFI proposal, 1982; 151214 (Box 104, Folder 2134)
    - X-Ray research, N/A; 151215 (Box 104, Folder 2135)
    - British Television, 1982-1985; 151216 (Box 104, Folder 2136)
    - California contact lists, N/A; 151217 (Box 104, Folder 2137)
    - Corporation for Public Broadcasting proposal, 1982-1984; 151218 (Box 104, Folder 2138)
    - Astrea Foundation, 1985; 151219 (Box 104, Folder 2139)
    - C.S. Fund, 1983-1985; 151220 (Box 104, Folder 2140)
    - Arca Foundation, 1984; 151221 (Box 104, Folder 2141)
    - The Film Fund, 1985; 151222 (Box 104, Folder 2142)
    - George Gund Foundation, 1983; 151223 (Box 104, Folder 2143)
    - Ruth Mott Fund, 1985; 151224 (Box 104, Folder 2144)
    - Center for Defense Information, 1982-1984; 151225 (Box 104, Folder 2145)
    - Geraldine Dodge Foundation, undated; 151226 (Box 104, Folder 2146)
    - Misc. Foundations, funding brochures, and inquiries, 1982-1988; 151227 (Box 104, Folder 2147)
    - Fundraising as of 10/85, 1985; 151228 (Box 105, Folder 2148)
      Offsite Barcode: 31142042236110
    - Accounts Payable, 1985-1987; 151229 (Box 105, Folder 2149)
    - Errors and Omissions Insurance, 1981-1987; 151230 (Box 105, Folder 2150)
    - David Byrne contract, 1983-1986; 151277 (Box 105, Folder 2151)
    - Film Festivals, 1986; 151278 (Box 105, Folder 2152)
    - Text & photo rights info, 1983-1985; 151279 (Box 105, Folder 2153)
    - Revised budgets & other financials, 10/15/85, 1985; 151280 (Box 105, Folder 2154)
    - Film Festivals, 1981-1985; 151281 (Box 105, Folder 2155)
    - Los Angeles trip, 1985; 151282 (Box 105, Folder 2156)
    - Promotional - correspondence, 1986; 151283 (Box 105, Folder 2157)
    - Receipts (Federal Express), 1986-1987; 151284 (Box 105, Folder 2158)
    - Mail for Marian Godfrey, 1986-1987; 151288 (Box 105, Folder 2159)
    - The Cinema Guild distribution files, 1987-1991; 151289 (Box 105, Folder 2160)
    - Film Forum screenings info, 1986; 151290 (Box 105, Folder 2161)
    - Media Space, Inc. - Distribution representation agreement, 1986-1987; 151291 (Box 105, Folder 2162)
    - Public Broadcasting info, 1986-1989; 151292 (Box 105, Folder 2163)
    - "On Screen" - N. California Women's Film Fest, 1986-1987; 151295 (Box 105, Folder 2164)
    - San Francisco Film Festival, 1987; 151296 (Box 105, Folder 2165)
    - Seattle Intl. Film Festival, 1986-1987; 151298 (Box 105, Folder 2166)
    - Anti-nuclear & Anti-war groups info, 1986-1987; 151304 (Box 105, Folder 2167)
    - Spoleto Festival program copy, 1983; 151305 (Box 105, Folder 2168)
    - Financial files, 1986-1989; 151306 (Box 105, Folder 2169)
    - Contributions - correspondence, 1989; 151307 (Box 105, Folder 2170)
    - Fundraising, financial, and other misc. files, 1984-1985; 151308 (Box 105, Folder 2171)
    - Gifts & grants, 1982-1985; 151309 (Box 105, Folder 2172)
    - Credits & special thanks, N/A; 151310 (Box 105, Folder 2173)
    - Insurance files, 1982-1985; 151311 (Box 105, Folder 2174)
    - Memos, 1985; 151312 (Box 105, Folder 2175)
    - Post-production worksheets - editing, sound, opticals, 1985-1986; 151313 (Box 106, Folder 2176)
      Offsite Barcode: 31142042236128
    - Misc. promo & press, 1980-1986; 151314 (Box 106, Folder 2177)
    - Titles, credits, intertitles, N/A; 151315 (Box 106, Folder 2179)
    - Photo credit labels, N/A; 151316 (Box 106, Folder 2180)
    - Radio Vision Intl. & Michael Sporn Animation press kits, 151317 (Box 106, Folder 2182)
    - Research - atomic energy, N/A; 151318 (Box 106, Folder 2182)
    - Seeing Red film files, ca. 1984; 151319 (Box 106, Folder 2183)
    - Ron Mann film project files, 1981-1984; 151320 (Box 106, Folder 2184)
    - Rights info - correspondence, agreements, etc., 1986; 151321 (Box 106, Folder 2185)
    - Copyright files, 1987; 151322 (Box 106, Folder 2186)
    - Clip rights clearances, N/A; 151323 (Box 106, Folder 2187)
    - PBS files - correspondence, contract, mailing list, etc., 1983-1989; 151324 (Box 106, Folder 2188)
    - Seibu Corp. distribution info, 1987; 151325 (Box 106, Folder 2189)
    - Northwest Film & Video Center (Oregon Art Institute), 1987; 151326 (Box 106, Folder 2190)
    - Reception info, 1987; 151327 (Box 106, Folder 2191)
    - Press and Promotional material, 1985-1986; 151328 (Box 106, Folder 2192)
    - American Film & Video Festival, 1986-1987; 151329 (Box 106, Folder 2193)
    - Antwerp Intl. Film Festival, 1986-1987; 151330 (Box 106, Folder 2194)
    - Atlanta FIlm & Video Festival, 1986-1987; 151331 (Box 106, Folder 2195)
    - Baltimore Intl. Film Festival, 1987; 151332 (Box 106, Folder 2196)
    - Berlin Film Festival, 1986-1987; 151333 (Box 106, Folder 2197)
    - Independent Film Festival (Brazil), 1987; 151334 (Box 106, Folder 2198)
    - Cleveland Intl. Film Festival, 1987; 151335 (Box 106, Folder 2199)
    - Festival Intl. de Creteil, 1987; 151336 (Box 106, Folder 2200)
    - Florence Film Festival, 1986-1987; 151337 (Box 106, Folder 2201)
    - Hong Kong Film Festival, 1987; 151338 (Box 106, Folder 2202)
    - Los Angeles Film Festival, 1986-1987; 151339 (Box 106, Folder 2203)
    - Festival of Festivals (Toronto Film Festival), 1986; 151340 (Box 106, Folder 2204)
    - USA Film Festival, 1986; 151341 (Box 106, Folder 2205)
    - US Film Festival (Sundance), 1986-1989; 151342 (Box 106, Folder 2206)
    - Finances - film account (Chemical Bank), 1983-1984; 151374 (Box 107, Folder 2207)
      Offsite Barcode: 31142042236136
    - Finances - film account (Chemical Bank), 1982-1983; 151375 (Box 107, Folder 2208)
    - Budgets, 1982-1984; 151376 (Box 107, Folder 2209)